### CONTACT

+66 54-1439-55

Atithiya.inthorn@gmail.com Bangkok 10800, Thailand linkedin.com/in/atithiya github.com/Atithiya

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS / Bootstrap / Tailwind
- Javascript / React Js
- Node JS / Express JS
- MongoDB / SQL
- Git / Github
- Figma

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Growth mindset
- Persistence
- Teamwork

### **LANGUAGE**

- Thai (Native)
- English (TOEIC 790)

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of laws** (2017 - 2020) Ramkhamhaeng University

### **CERTIFICATED**

- AML/CTPF: Anti-Money

   Laundering and Counter
   Terrorism and Proliferation of
   Weapon of Mass Destruction
   Financing Certified by the Anti-Money Laundering Office
   (Thailand)
- Course Software Testing Manual By Kru P' Beam

### **LICENSE**

• Attorney At Law License

# **ATITHIYA INTHORN**

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a graduate of Generation JSD Boot Camp. Previously, I was in the document verification industry for 2 years. The experience allowed me to be oriented to detail and I'm willing to learn new technology. I am looking forward to applying my previous work experiences and newly developed technical skills to launch my career in a tech field.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Junior Software Developer Cohort 5 Generation Thailand

July - Oct 2023

- Developed a workout tracking website with both desktop and mobile-responsive web designs using the MERN Stack, which includes MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, and Node.js.
- Acquired essential behavioral skills for both the workplace and personal life, including a growth mindset, effective communication, personal responsibility, and persistence.
- Developed multiple mini-projects using HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, and React JS, including CRUD React JS projects.

Quality Control - Document Quality June 2022 - June 2023 PRTR Group Co.,Ltd.

### Operating for ShopeeXpress (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

- Verified the employees' work to verify whether the delivery of the parcel complies with the process with oriented to detail skill.
- Verified procedure and privacy complied to the PDPA law by analyzing the submitted data.
- Applied problem-solving skills to handle clients who complaint over an employee's behavior.

### KYC Officer April 2021 - June 2022 Workmate Solution Recruitment Co., Ltd. Operating for Bitkub Online Co., Ltd

- Verified the identity verification lists, In advance of creating a customer account.
- Investigated high-risk of client's occupation with curiosity, reported where necessary, and obtained all necessary documentation to complete the customer profile.
- Completed daily KPIs and was promoted to Data Cleansing position.

## **PROJECT**

### **KeepFit (Workout application)**

• Developed a workout tracking application geared towards elderly users, facilitating the logging of daily workouts and presenting a user-friendly dashboard.